wpbeaveraddons.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy - PowerPack Beaver Builder Addon

We value the trust you place in us. That is why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and reliable customer information privacy policy.

To learn about the information gathering and dissemination practices by IdeaBox Creations, please read the following statement.

### Collection of Personal Identification Information

When you use our website, we may collect personal identification information in a variety of ways such as when users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form we make available on our Site.

If you prefer, you can browse the website anonymously which means without telling us whom you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you provide us with your personal information, you are not anonymous to us.

Our primary goal in gathering personal information is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our website to make your experience safer and more comfortable. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in specific Site-related activities.

Collection of Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our Site. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Sites, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Use of Information / Profile Data/ Demographic

We use personal information to provide the services you request. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; process payments; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about offers, products, and updates; customize your experience; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

IdeaBox Creations may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

– To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

– To process payments

We may use the information users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature

To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

– To promote healthy promotion strategies

To use the user’s information to build more trust with the brand and promote business in a healthy manner.

– To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send user information and updates pertaining to your order. It may also be used to respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Cookies

Our Site may use “Cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. For promoting business, we might share information regarding new and old orders on our website to build trust and enhance user experience. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. Also, these sites or services, including their content and links, may constantly be changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Choice/Opt-Out

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

If you want to remove your contact information from all https://wpbeaveraddons.com/ lists and newsletters, please visit unsubscribe.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Consent

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us here](https://wpbeaveraddons.com/contact/).
